egmnow.com 2019-06-26

# Privacy Policy – EGMNOW

**EGM MEDIA, LLC PRIVACY POLICY**

Thank you for visiting this EGM Media, LLC (“EGM”) publication. Your privacy is important to  
us and to better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our information practices  
and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used by EGM. 

**What Data Is Collected By EGM?**

Through EGM print publications, digital publications, websites, and other media, you can order  
products, enter contests, vote in polls or otherwise express an opinion, subscribe to one of our  
services, or participate in one of our online forums or communities either hosted by EGM or by  
a third-party. You are able to visit much of this website and enjoy many EGM publications and  
promotions without providing any personally identifiable information. Sometimes, however, we  
do need your personally identifiable information to provide you with the products and services  
that you request. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected at these  
pages and elsewhere include, but are not limited to: name, address, e-mail address, telephone  
number, fax number, credit card information, and information about your interests in and use of  
various products, programs, and services. 

At some EGM sites and through certain promotions, you can submit information about other  
people. For example, you might submit a person’s name and e-mail address to send an electronic  
message and, if you order a gift online or offline and want it sent directly to the recipient, you  
might submit the recipient’s name and address. The types of personally identifiable information  
that may be collected about other people at these pages include: recipient’s name, address, e-mail  
address, and telephone number. 

For certain promotions, only persons who provide us with the requested personally identifiable  
information will be able to order products, programs, and services or otherwise participate in the  
promotion’s activities and offerings. 

We also may collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit many of our  
web pages such as the type of browser you are using, the type of operating system you are using,  
and the domain name of your Internet service provider. 

**How We Use the Information**

We may use the information you provide about yourself to fulfill your requests for our products,  
programs, and services, to respond to your inquiries about offerings, and to offer you other  
products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you. 

We sometimes use this information to communicate with you, such as to notify you when you  
have won one of our contests or when we make changes to subscriber agreements, to fulfill a  
request by you for an online or digital publication, or to contact you about your account with us. 

We use the information that you provide about others to enable us to send them your gifts or  
cards. From time to time, we also may use this information to offer our products, programs, or  
services to them. 

If you choose to submit content for publication (e.g., a “letter to our editors”), we may publish  
your name, screen name, and other information you have provided to us without further  
notification or request for permission. 

The information we collect in connection with our online forums and communities is used to  
provide an interactive experience. We use this information to facilitate participation in these  
online forums and communities and, from time to time, to offer you products, programs, or  
services. 

We sometimes use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the  
design and content of our publications and websites and to enable us to personalize your Internet  
experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze site usage, as well as to  
offer you products, programs, or services. 

We will disclose information we maintain when required by law, in response to a court order or  
a subpoena. We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency’s  
request. 

Agents, contractors, and other companies that may provide services to EGM, including, but not  
limited to, EGM Digital Media, LLC, may receive access to personally identifiable information  
and your use of the site grants EGM the right to transfer such information without notice.  
Agents, contractors, and other companies that may provide services to EGM are required to  
protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Notice by, for example,  
not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing  
for EGM. 

We may transfer your personally identifiable information to other EGM offices for internal  
management and administrative purposes. Your personal data will be transferred to other EGM  
offices where necessary for the performance or conclusion of our contractual obligations to you  
or for your benefit. Transfers of personally identifiable information may also be made where  
necessary for the establishment, exercise, or defense of legal claims. 

Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of  
information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect  
will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Notice. Inadvertent  
disclosures may result, for example, when third parties misrepresent their identities in asking the  
site for access to personally identifiable information about themselves for purposes of correcting  
possible factual errors in the data. 

**Privacy Options**

You may opt-out of participating with any EGM website, product, or service at any time by  
emailing [privacy@egmnow.net](mailto:privacy@egmnow.net). 

**Collection and Use of Information by Third-Party Sites and Sponsors**

Some of our sites contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different than  
ours. You should consult the other sites’ privacy notices, as we have no control over information  
that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties. 

EGM sites sometimes may offer contests, sweepstakes, promotions, editorial features, or other  
activities or offerings that are sponsored or co-sponsored by or presented with identified third  
parties. By virtue of your participation in such activities or offerings, the personally identifiable  
information that you voluntarily submit may be provided to both the EGM site and the third  
parties. EGM has no control over the third parties’ use of this information. 

EGM sites may use reputable third parties to present or serve the advertisements that you may  
see at its web pages and to conduct research about the advertisements. This privacy notice does  
not cover any use of information that such third parties may have collected from you or the  
methods used by the third-parties to collect that information (e.g., cookies, web beacons and  
clear gifs). 

**Cookies**

To enhance your online experience we use “cookies.” Cookies are text files we place in your  
computer’s browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-  
mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this  
information to us by, for example, registering at one of our sites. However, once you choose to  
furnish the site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the  
data stored in the cookie. 

We use cookies to understand Internet usage and to improve our content, offerings, and  
advertisements. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our web  
pages (e.g. to recognize you by name when you return to our site), save your password in  
password-protected areas, and enable you to use shopping carts on our sites. We also may use  
cookies to offer you products, programs, or services. Similarly, as part of an arrangement with  
our business partners (including, those who present or serve the advertisements that you see on  
our web pages) we may also access cookies placed by others and allow others to access certain  
cookies placed by us. 

We may also use small pieces of code called “web beacons” or “clear gifs” to collect anonymous  
and aggregate advertising metrics, such as counting page views, promotion views, or advertising  
responses. These “web beacons” may be used to deliver cookies that conform to our cookie  
policy. 

**Our Commitment to Security**

EGM always strives to engage third-parties that we believe put in place appropriate physical,  
electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access,  
maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect. 

**How You Can Access or Correct Information**

To inquire about personally identifiable information that this EGM site has collected about you,  
or how to correct factual errors in such information, please email us at [privacy@egmnow.net](mailto:privacy@egmnow.net). 

To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity  
before granting access or making corrections. 

**No Information From Children Under the Age of 13**

Protecting the privacy of young children is important to us and if you are under the age of 13  
please do not register on any EGM website, attempt to receive any EGM digital publication,  
or provide us with any personal information to us, including your name, address, telephone  
number, and/or e-mail address. EGM will, upon learning that personal information from a  
child under the age of 13 has been collected, delete that information as quickly as possible. If  
you believe we may have received information from a child under age 13 please contact us at  
[privacy@egmnow.net](mailto:privacy@egmnow.net). 

**Changes to this Notice**

This Notice may be changed by EGM. The revised Notice will be posted to this page so that you  
are aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we may  
disclose it. 

**How to Contact Us**

If you have any questions or concerns about the EGM Privacy Notice or its implementation  
please contact us via email at [privacy@egmnow.net](mailto:privacy@egmnow.net) or at the following address: 

EGM Media, LLC  
Attention: Customer Service  
8840 Wilshire Blvd., Third Floor,  
Beverly Hills, CA 90211 

This following applies to users from countries that are a Member State of the European Union and is intended to be supplementary to our existing Privacy Policy.  
EGM Media, LLC is the data controller for processing of information defined as personal data under applicable data protection law (“Personal Data”). 

**LEGAL BASIS FOR DATA PROCESSING**

We process Personal Data for the purposes set out in the Privacy Policy. Our legal basis to process Personal Data includes processing that is: necessary for the performance of the contract between you and EGM Media, LLC (for example, to provide you with the services you request and to identify and authenticate you so you may use the website); necessary to comply with legal requirements (for example, to comply with applicable accounting rules and to make mandatory disclosures to law enforcement); necessary for our legitimate interests (for example, to manage our relationship with you and to improve the website and our services); and based on consent by our customers (for example, to communicate with you about our products and services and provide you with marketing information), which may subsequently be withdrawn at any time by contacting us (using the contact instructions below) without affecting the lawfulness of processing based on consent before its withdrawal. 

**EU DATA SUBJECT RIGHTS**

The EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) provides certain rights for EU data subjects. You may decline to share certain personal information with us, in which case we may not be able to provide some of the features and functionality of our website. These rights include, in accordance with applicable law, the right to object to or request the restriction of processing of your Personal Data, and to request access to, rectification, erasure and portability of your own Personal Data. Requests should be submitted by contacting us (using the contact instructions below). 

You may make changes to the personal information collected by our account registration pages by logging into the appropriate Service and updating the account settings page. We will make commercially reasonable efforts to provide you reasonable access to your personal information within 30 days of your access request to the contact address below. We provide this access so that you may review, make corrections, or request deletion of your personal information. If we cannot honor your request within 30 days, we will inform you when we will be able to provide such access. If for some reason access is denied, we will provide an explanation as to why access is denied. When technically feasible, at your request, we will provide your personal data to you or transmit it directly to another controller. 

We will retain your personal information for as long as it is reasonably necessary for the purposes set out in the Privacy Policy, considering the time period reasonably necessary to: provide services to you; exercise the choices and rights you have requested; comply with our contractual obligations; enforce our terms for use of the website; and, comply with legal and regulatory requirements. 

If you have any unresolved privacy concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily after contacting us, you have the right to contact the appropriate EU Data Protection Authority and lodge a complaint. 

**THIRD PARTY ONLINE ADVERTISING**

We enable certain third party advertising exchanges to place advertisements on our sites. With your consent, those advertising exchanges collect your IP address and/or a unique advertising ID that is used by the advertising exchange to identify you across the internet. 

The European Digital Advertising Alliance {“EDAA”} has developed a guide to online behavioural advertising and has developed an opt out page to manage online behavioural advertising preferences with EDAA member companies available at [www.YourOnlineChoices.com](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/). To find out more about how you can manage cookies and the other similar technologies, [click here for additional information](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/). 

To control Publisher Common ID settings click here. 

**AUTOMATED DECISION MAKING**

We use automated decision-making technologies, including profiling, to support our data processing activities. These include services designed to develop and provide advertising tailored to your interests and to customize the content you see when you visit an EGM Media, LLC website. 

**CONTACT US**

For all EU Data Subject Rights requests, you must put the statement “Your EU Data Subject Rights” in the subject field of your request and include in the request the name of the services with respect to which you are requesting the information, as well as your contact information. 

If you need further assistance, please [contact us](mailto:support@egmnow.net). If you would prefer to submit your questions or comments by mail, please send a letter to the address below: 

EGM Media, LLC  
ATTN: Privacy  
21781 Ventura Blvd.,  
Suite 315,  
Woodland Hills, CA 91364
